clbuzz.com 2011-12-31

# CLBuzz – Complete Sports Buzz » x-privacy policy

**Privacy Policy for www.clbuzz.com**

If you require any more  information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to  contact us by email at support@clbuzz.com.

At www.clbuzz.com,  the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy  document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by  www.clbuzz.com and how it is used.

 **Log Files**  
Like many  other Web sites, www.clbuzz.com makes use of log files. The information  inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of  browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit  pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s  movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and  other such information are not linked to any information that is personally  identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.clbuzz.com does  not use cookies.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a  third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.clbuzz.com.  
.::  Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their  visit to www.clbuzz.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may  opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content  network privacy policy at the following URL -  http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners  may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include  ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks  use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.clbuzz.com  send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when  this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons )  may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of  their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you  see.

www.clbuzz.com has no access to or control over these cookies  that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the  respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed  information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out  of certain practices. www.clbuzz.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and  we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual  browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific  web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
